[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "questionType": "MATH",
    "question": "2+2=",
    "answerA": "4",
    "answerB": "1",
    "answerC": "2",
    "answerD": "6",
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "questionType": "MATH",
    "question": "2+5=",
    "answerA": "4",
    "answerB": "7",
    "answerC": "2",
    "answerD": "6",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "questionType": "MATH",
    "question": "3+2=",
    "answerA": "4",
    "answerB": "1",
    "answerC": "5",
    "answerD": "6",
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "questionType": "MATH",
    "question": "3+7=",
    "answerA": "4",
    "answerB": "10",
    "answerC": "5",
    "answerD": "6",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "questionType": "MATH",
    "question": "2*3=",
    "answerA": "4",
    "answerB": "1",
    "answerC": "5",
    "answerD": "6",
    "correctAnswer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "questionType": "MATH",
    "question": "4/2=",
    "answerA": "4",
    "answerB": "1",
    "answerC": "2",
    "answerD": "6",
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "questionType": "MATH",
    "question": "3+3=",
    "answerA": "9",
    "answerB": "1",
    "answerC": "5",
    "answerD": "6",
    "correctAnswer": "A"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "questionType": "MATH",
    "question": "4*0=",
    "answerA": "4",
    "answerB": "1",
    "answerC": "0",
    "answerD": "6",
    "correctAnswer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "questionType": "MATH",
    "question": "1*8=",
    "answerA": "4",
    "answerB": "8",
    "answerC": "5",
    "answerD": "6",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "questionType": "MATH",
    "question": "3+8=",
    "answerA": "4",
    "answerB": "11",
    "answerC": "5",
    "answerD": "6",
    "correctAnswer": "B"
  }
]
